Sarah Beecroft

Digital Marketer with over 8 years of experience writing engaging copy for B2C campaigns, crafting promotional materials, and fueling positive engagement on social media. Passionate about meaningful work and constant growth.

Looking to break into the world of web development upon graduating University of Washington Coding Bootcamp in 2019.

Skills

- Content writing for blog posts, social media, and promotional campaigns
- Setting up and monitoring email campaigns from start to finish
- Leadership and management skills

- Experienced in: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, MailChimp, Office 365, Sprinklr, TweetDeck, Wordpress, and Yesmail
- Beginner HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript/jQuery skills

Experience

DATES: MAY 2016 - PRESENT

JeffreyM Consulting (Microsoft) - Bellevue, WA Xbox Community Manager

- Monitors all inbound content on Xbox social media channels including: Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and YouTube
- Reactively engages with fans, prospects, and customers on official Xbox channels
- Discovers trending topics, themes, and consumer interests and needs across social media
- Creates and distributes weekly/monthly reports on social activity
- Brainstorms campaign and proactive post ideas with Xbox marketing team based on trends
- Assists with customer support and technical inquiries

Social Listening Manager

- Managed social listening team of 6 for Microsoft project
- Compiled keyword lists and scanned social media for keywords
- Put together reports on trends/themes based on keyword listening
- Managerial duties such as: team scheduling, weekly 1:1s, and performance reviews
- Tested key product features for quality assurance

Retail Community Manager

- Improved customer satisfaction and built customer insights by monitoring Surface and PC Accessory product reviews at online retailers, primarily Amazon
- Crafted individual responses to consumers and prospects regarding Surface and PC Accessory devices
- Provided answers to Surface and PC Accessory product questions online
- Managed multiple email aliases and responded directly to email inquiries regarding support and product questions

DATES: SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2016

TaskEasy - Salt Lake City, UT Email & Content Manager

- Wrote, designed, and monitored all company marketing and informational email campaigns
- Redesigned and updated all company transactional emails (order confirmation, order updates, etc.)
- Wrote fun and informative content for website and company blog
- Brainstormed ideas with Marketing team for email campaigns, promotions, and sales
- Set up logistics behind contests and promotions
- Monitored and responded to customer reviews via ShopperApproved
- Set up and monitored all paid social media campaigns on Twitter and Facebook
- Engaged with customers and prospects on Twitter and Facebook

Education

DATES: FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

University of Washington Coding Boot Camp Part-Time Full Stack Program

- Learning MERN stack
- In progress

Activities

- Won Employee of the Month at both JeffreyM Consulting and TaskEasy
- Completed HTML/CSS/Javascript courses with Codecademy
- Participated in Ragnar Relay Wasatch Back with team of 11 coworkers
- Enjoys reading, music, film, and the outdoors